Dicky Darmawan

Tiban McDermott blok K no.20, (+62) 87773592720, dickytwillio@gmail.com

PROFILE

As specializes front-end developer in building the visual and interactive aspects of websites and web applications. They work with technologies like Next.Js, TailwindCSS, Vue.Js and Laravel to create user-friendly interfaces that ensure a seamless user experience. Their role involves collaborating with designers and back-end developers to bring design concepts to life while optimizing performance and responsiveness across different devices.

EDUCATION

Politeknik Negeri Batam

Informatics Engineering

Batam 2021 - present

Latest GPA: 3.70 (scale of 4.00)

SMA Negeri 4 Batam

Social Program

Batam

2016 – 2019

- Final average score: 80 (scale of 100)
- Member of Praja Muda Karana in 2016

WORKING EXPERIENCES

B One Consulting

Batam

Front-End Developer – Internship

March 2024 – August 2024

 For 6 months, I worked on a website project, namely Bali Smart Investment, and where I made it page by page, starting from home, services and so on.

Pt.Total Printing Indonesia

Batam

Technician Engineering – Employee

April 2021 – January 2022

 Works in the technician engineering division, tasked with managing and maintaining photocopy machines, as well as carrying out routine service every month. Working in the barista section, designing unique and high quality coffee drinks, taking orders and serving customers and maintaining the cleanliness and hygiene of the shop.

PORTOFOLIO

https://dickydarmawan-hazel.vercel.app/

KEY SKILLS

- Critical Thinking, Decision Make Ability and Strategic Thinking.
- Good Communication, Problem Solving, Recruitment and Selection Skills.
- Typography, color theory, prototyping, usability testing, responsive Design.
- Next.Js Knowledge & Agile and easy to adapt.
- Proficient in designing websites using the CSS TailwindCSS framework.
- You can create website-based applications with create, read, update and delete features using Vue.Js and Laravel.